The
unemployment rate for
16 to
24 year
olds- Mm-hmm.
Mm-hmm, right has
moved to 12%.
12%, big
increase. And
what is that
saying? That's
saying that
entry-level jobs
are not being
created the
way they
used to be.
To those
people, I
say, you
must have in
your mind
an idea
for a new
business, something
that frustrates
you, an unmet
need. Well,
now you can
go to ChatGPT,
you can
go to Grok,
and you
can have an
assistant help
you build out
that business.
Just interview
for jobs, but
also think about
new business
ideas. I think
we're going
to see entrepreneurial
explosion
here. Well,
and speaking of
entrepreneurial
explosion, I think about
how long you
have certainly
been